{"test_questions": [[{"question": "CORPULENT", "opta": "Lean", "optb": "Gaunt", "optc": "Emaciated", "optd": "Obese", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "BRIEF", "opta": "Limited", "optb": "Small", "optc": "Little", "optd": "Short", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "EMBEZZLE", "opta": "Misappropriate", "optb": "Balance", "optc": "Remunerate", "optd": "Clear", "ans": "A", "explanation": "Main Entry: embezzle\n\nPart of Speech: verb\n\nDefinition: steal money, often from employer\n\nSynonyms: abstract, defalcate, filch, forge, loot, misapply, misappropriate, misuse, peculate, pilfer, purloin, put hand in cookie jar, put hand in till, skim, thieve\n\nAntonyms:\t compensate, give, pay, reimburse, return"}, {"question": "VENT", "opta": "Opening", "optb": "Stodge", "optc": "End", "optd": "Past tense of go", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "AUGUST", "opta": "Common", "optb": "Ridiculous", "optc": "Dignified", "optd": "Petty", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CANNY", "opta": "Obstinate", "optb": "Handsome", "optc": "Clever", "optd": "Stout", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ALERT", "opta": "Energetic", "optb": "Observant", "optc": "Intelligent", "optd": "Watchful", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "WARRIOR", "opta": "Soldier", "optb": "Sailor", "optc": "Pirate", "optd": "Spy", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DISTANT", "opta": "Far", "optb": "Removed", "optc": "Reserved", "optd": "Separate", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ADVERSITY", "opta": "Failure", "optb": "Helplessness", "optc": "Misfortune", "optd": "Crisis", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Adversity is a very difficult or unfavourable situation."}, {"question": "FAKE", "opta": "Original", "optb": "Imitation", "optc": "Trustworthy", "optd": "Loyal", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INDICT", "opta": "Condemn", "optb": "Reprimand", "optc": "Accuse", "optd": "Allege", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Meanings: formally accuse of a crime (Law); accuse, charge, criticize"}, {"question": "STRINGENT", "opta": "Dry", "optb": "Strained", "optc": "Rigorous", "optd": "Shrill", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "LAMENT", "opta": "Complain", "optb": "Comment", "optc": "Condone", "optd": "Console", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HESITATED", "opta": "Stopped", "optb": "Paused", "optc": "Slowed", "optd": "Postponed", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "RESCUE", "opta": "Command", "optb": "Help", "optc": "Defence", "optd": "Safety", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ATTEMPT", "opta": "Serve", "optb": "Explore", "optc": "Try", "optd": "Explain", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FORAY", "opta": "Maraud", "optb": "Contest", "optc": "Ranger", "optd": "Intuition", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "RECKLESS", "opta": "Courageous", "optb": "Rash", "optc": "Bold", "optd": "Daring", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CONSEQUENCES", "opta": "Results", "optb": "Conclusions", "optc": "Difficulties", "optd": "Applications", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "IMPROVEMENT", "opta": "Advancement", "optb": "Betterment", "optc": "Promotion", "optd": "Preference", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INEBRIATE", "opta": "Dreamy", "optb": "Stupefied", "optc": "Unsteady", "optd": "Drunken", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "STERILE", "opta": "Barren", "optb": "Arid", "optc": "Childless", "optd": "Dry", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ABJECT", "opta": "Challenge", "optb": "Miserable", "optc": "Deny", "optd": "Disobey", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MOVING", "opta": "Taking", "optb": "Toying", "optc": "Shifting", "optd": "Turning", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "IRONIC", "opta": "Inflexible", "optb": "Bitter", "optc": "Good-natured", "optd": "Disguisedly sarcastic", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "TIMID", "opta": "Fast", "optb": "Slow", "optc": "Medium", "optd": "Shy", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "EXTRICATE", "opta": "Pull", "optb": "Free", "optc": "Tie", "optd": "Complicate", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "NEUTRAL", "opta": "Unbiased", "optb": "Non-aligned", "optc": "Undecided", "optd": "Indifferent", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SHALLOW", "opta": "Artificial", "optb": "Superficial", "optc": "Foolish", "optd": "Worthless", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DIVERSION", "opta": "Amusement", "optb": "Distortion", "optc": "Deviation", "optd": "Bylane", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INSOLVENT", "opta": "Poor", "optb": "Bankrupt", "optc": "Penniless", "optd": "Broke", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INEXPLICABLE", "opta": "Confusing", "optb": "Unaccountable", "optc": "Chaotic", "optd": "Unconnected", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FEEBLE", "opta": "Weak", "optb": "Vain", "optc": "Arrogant", "optd": "Sick", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "TRANSIENT", "opta": "Transparent", "optb": "Fleeting", "optc": "Feeble", "optd": "Fanciful", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "BARE", "opta": "Uncovered", "optb": "Tolerate", "optc": "Clear", "optd": "Neat", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "REPEAL", "opta": "Sanction", "optb": "Perpetuate", "optc": "Pass", "optd": "Cancel", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SALACITY", "opta": "Bliss", "optb": "Depression", "optc": "Indecency", "optd": "Recession", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ECSTATIC", "opta": "Animated", "optb": "Bewildered", "optc": "Enraptured", "optd": "Illful", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ADMONISH", "opta": "Punish", "optb": "Curse", "optc": "Dismiss", "optd": "Reprimand", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DILIGENT", "opta": "Progressive", "optb": "Brilliant", "optc": "Inventive", "optd": "Hard-working", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PIOUS", "opta": "Pure", "optb": "Pretentious", "optc": "Clean", "optd": "Devout", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "BROWSE", "opta": "Heal", "optb": "Deceive", "optc": "Examine", "optd": "Strike", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INFREQUENT", "opta": "Never", "optb": "Usual", "optc": "Rare", "optd": "Sometimes", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Infrequent means happening rarely, uncommon."}, {"question": "RESTRAINT", "opta": "Hindrance", "optb": "Repression", "optc": "Obstacle", "optd": "Restriction", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DEIFY", "opta": "Flatter", "optb": "Challenge", "optc": "Worship", "optd": "Face", "ans": "C", "explanation": "If someone is deified, they are considered to be a god or are regarded with very great respect."}, {"question": "HARBINGER", "opta": "Messenger", "optb": "Steward", "optc": "Forerunner", "optd": "Pilot", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "VENUE", "opta": "Place", "optb": "Agenda", "optc": "Time", "optd": "Duration", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CANDID", "opta": "Apparent", "optb": "Explicit", "optc": "Frank", "optd": "Bright", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MELD", "opta": "To soothe", "optb": "Merge", "optc": "Purchase", "optd": "Glisten", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "LYNCH", "opta": "Hang", "optb": "Madden", "optc": "Kill", "optd": "Shoot", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "TORTURE", "opta": "Torment", "optb": "Chastisement", "optc": "Harassment", "optd": "Terror", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ABUNDANT", "opta": "Ripe", "optb": "Cheap", "optc": "Plenty", "optd": "Absent", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ENTIRE", "opta": "Part", "optb": "Quarter", "optc": "Whole", "optd": "Half", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DESTITUTION", "opta": "Humility", "optb": "Moderation", "optc": "Poverty", "optd": "Beggary", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Destitution: Poverty so extreme that one lacks the means to provide for oneself."}, {"question": "WRETCHED", "opta": "Poor", "optb": "Foolish", "optc": "Insane", "optd": "Strained", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INTIMIDATE", "opta": "To hint", "optb": "Frighten", "optc": "Bluff", "optd": "Harass", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CANTANKEROUS", "opta": "Quarrelsome", "optb": "Rash", "optc": "Disrespectful", "optd": "Noisy", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "RANT", "opta": "Praise inordinately", "optb": "Formalise", "optc": "To preach noisily", "optd": "Treat with screen", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ZANY", "opta": "Clown", "optb": "Pet", "optc": "Thief", "optd": "Magician", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "TACITURNITY", "opta": "Dumbness", "optb": "Changeablemess", "optc": "Hesitation", "optd": "Reserve", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MASSACRE", "opta": "Murder", "optb": "Stab", "optc": "Assassinate", "optd": "Slaughter", "ans": "D", "explanation": "MASSACRE means slaughter, kill a large number of people violently."}, {"question": "KEN", "opta": "Ignorance", "optb": "Witness", "optc": "Trial", "optd": "Knowledge", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "WARY", "opta": "Sad", "optb": "vigilant", "optc": "Distorted", "optd": "Tired", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "RABBLE", "opta": "Mob", "optb": "Noise", "optc": "Roar", "optd": "Rubbish", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MAYHEM", "opta": "Jubilation", "optb": "Havoc", "optc": "Excitement", "optd": "Defeat", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PONDER", "opta": "Think", "optb": "Evaluate", "optc": "Anticipate", "optd": "Increase", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CONNOISSEUR", "opta": "Ignorant", "optb": "Lover of art", "optc": "Interpreter", "optd": "Delinquent", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SHIVER", "opta": "Feel", "optb": "Rock", "optc": "Tremble", "optd": "Move", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PRESTIGE", "opta": "Influence", "optb": "Quality", "optc": "Name", "optd": "Wealth", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "STRINGENT", "opta": "Tense", "optb": "Stringly", "optc": "Strict", "optd": "Causing to Shrink", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INSOMNIA", "opta": "Lethargy", "optb": "Sleeplessness", "optc": "Drunkenness", "optd": "Unconsciousness", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "LAUD", "opta": "Lord", "optb": "Eulogy", "optc": "Praise", "optd": "Extolled", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "REPERCUSSION", "opta": "Clever reply", "optb": "Recollection", "optc": "Remuneration", "optd": "Reaction", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "IMPROMPTU", "opta": "Offhand", "optb": "Unimportant", "optc": "Unreal", "optd": "Effective", "ans": "A", "explanation": "An impromptu action is one that you do without planning or organizing it in advance."}, {"question": "FRUGALITY", "opta": "Foolishness", "optb": "Extremity", "optc": "Enthusiasm", "optd": "Economy", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CORRESPONDENCE", "opta": "Agreements", "optb": "Contracts", "optc": "Documents", "optd": "Letters", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ASCEND", "opta": "Leap", "optb": "Grow", "optc": "Deviate", "optd": "Mount", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FURORE", "opta": "Excitement", "optb": "Worry", "optc": "Flux", "optd": "Anteroom", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SYNOPSIS", "opta": "Index", "optb": "Mixture", "optc": "Summary", "optd": "Puzzles", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "TURN UP", "opta": "Land up", "optb": "Show up", "optc": "Crop up", "optd": "Come up", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "VIGOUR", "opta": "Strength", "optb": "Boldness", "optc": "Warmth", "optd": "Enthusism", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GARNISH", "opta": "Paint", "optb": "Garner", "optc": "Adorn", "optd": "Abuse", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MENDACIOUS", "opta": "Full of Confidence", "optb": "False", "optc": "Encouraging", "optd": "Provocative", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GARRULITY", "opta": "Credulity", "optb": "Senility", "optc": "Loquaciousness", "optd": "Speciousness", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MOROSE", "opta": "Annoyed", "optb": "Gloomy", "optc": "Moody", "optd": "Displeased", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "VORACIOUS", "opta": "Truthful", "optb": "Gluttonous", "optc": "Funny", "optd": "Venturous", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "AWAKENED", "opta": "Enlightened", "optb": "Realised", "optc": "Shook", "optd": "Waken", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GRATIFY", "opta": "Appreciate", "optb": "Frank", "optc": "Indulge", "optd": "Pacify", "ans": "C", "explanation": "If you are gratified by something, it gives you pleasure or satisfaction."}, {"question": "PRECARIOUS", "opta": "Cautious", "optb": "Critical", "optc": "Perilous", "optd": "Brittle", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INFAMY", "opta": "Dishonour", "optb": "Glory", "optc": "Integrity", "optd": "Reputation", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MASTERLY", "opta": "Crafty", "optb": "Skilful", "optc": "Meaningful", "optd": "Cruel", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SCINTILLATING", "opta": "Smouldering", "optb": "Glittering", "optc": "Touching", "optd": "Warming", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "TEPID", "opta": "Hot", "optb": "Warm", "optc": "Cold", "optd": "Boiling", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "VORACIOUS", "opta": "Wild", "optb": "Greedy", "optc": "Angry", "optd": "Quick", "ans": "B", "explanation": "If you describe a person, or their appetite for something, as voracious, you mean that they want a lot of something."}, {"question": "UNITE", "opta": "Unfold", "optb": "Unchain", "optc": "Combine", "optd": "Unhinge", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "COMBAT", "opta": "Conflict", "optb": "Quarrel", "optc": "Feud", "optd": "Fight", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "REFECTORY", "opta": "Restaurant", "optb": "Parlour", "optc": "Living Room", "optd": "Dining Room", "ans": "D", "explanation": "A refectory is a large room in a school, university, or other institution, where meals are served and eaten."}, {"question": "UNCOUTH", "opta": "Ungraceful", "optb": "Rough", "optc": "Slovenly", "optd": "Dirty", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ERROR", "opta": "Misadventure", "optb": "Misgiving", "optc": "Ambiguity", "optd": "Blunder", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "COMMENSURATE", "opta": "Measurable", "optb": "Proportionate", "optc": "Begining", "optd": "Appropriate", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DEBACLE", "opta": "Collapse", "optb": "Decline", "optc": "Defeat", "optd": "Disgrace", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GERMANE", "opta": "Responsible", "optb": "Logical", "optc": "Possible", "optd": "Relevant", "ans": "D", "explanation": "GERMANE - Relevant to a subject under consideration."}, {"question": "DISTINCTION", "opta": "Diffusion", "optb": "Disagreement", "optc": "Different", "optd": "Degree", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}